

# **Anh-Duy Tran**

M.Sc.Eng in Computer Security and Forensics

Date of birth: December 4

Gender: Male

**Phone:** +84865202491

**Email:** pakkunandy@gmail.com

Address: District 5, Ho Chi Minh City

Website: https://pakkunandy.github.io/

#### RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research focuses include many subjects in Computer and System Security, mostly in Computer Forensics, Mobile System Security, Privacy and Software Security. I work to help organizations to inspect digital evidence in the cyber-crime investigation process, to design a secured system and software. My research style is interdisciplinary in general. I am leveraging many techniques and knowledge from many domains to tackle real-world security-related problems and design a secure system.

### RESEARCH

My research interests include:

- Mobile System Security and Privacy.
- Software Security. Secure Coding.
- Computer Forensics: OS forensics and Memory Forensics.
- Imaging Security and Forensics.
- Social Engineering.
- Applied Cryptography: Searchable Encryption
- Penetration Testing.
- IoT and Hardware Security.

### **EDUCATION**

SEP 2017 - SEP 2019	EURECOM and Telecom Paris, France (Double Degree) M.Sc.Eng in Communication System Security Thesis grade: 20/20. Supervisor: Professor Davide Balzarotti
SEP 2016 - OCT 2018	John Von Neumann Institute - VNUHCM, Vietnam M.Sc in Data Science Working primarily in NLP and Regression
SEP 2012 - SEP 2016	University of Science - VNUHCM, Vietnam  B.Sc in Software Engineering  Thesis grade: 10/10. Supervisor: Professor Minh-Triet Tran

### **EXPERIENCE**

AUG 2020 - Now	KiteMetric Security Consultant
OCT 2019 - Now	VNUHCM - University of Science  Lecturer and Researcher in Computer Security  Researching Memory Forensics, Teaching in Computer Security

MAR 2019 - SEP 2019	EURECOM, France Memory Forensics Internship Supervisor: Prof. Davide Balzarotti. Final Grade: 20/20
JUL 2014 - AUG 2014	NEC Coprporation, Vietnam  Android Development Internship

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

2020	Computer Hacking Forensic Investigator Certification (CHFI), EC-Council
2016	Project Management, EURECOM
2015	Leadership Certification, JVN
2015	Summer Internship 2015 in NEC Vietnam Company
2013/2015	Merits of the Dean of Faculty of Information Technology for being in the Top 5 of Best Students in 2013 and 2015
2014	Participation second round Challenge Competition 2014

### **HONORS & AWARDS**

2017 - 2019	Eiffel Excellent Schlarship for Engineering Student.
2016	Valedictorian (1/500) in Information Technology, FIT - VNU-HCMUS.
2016	Second Prize in National Competition for Innovation of Students XVIII - Euréka
2016	Gold Medal of "Designing - Manufacturing - Application" Contest – Ho Chi Minh City
2016	Special prize of "Master Key" Contest - Ho Chi Minh City
2016	Consolation prize of 25th Young Information Technology Contest – Ho Chi Minh City
2015	Sunflower Mission Engineering and Technology Scholarship

### **LANGUAGES**

Mother tongue	Vietnamese
Other languages	English (Professional proficiency) French (Elementary)

## **UNIVERSITY SERVICES**

- Vice Chairman in The Associated Organ of Vietnamese Students' Association
- Member of the Executive Committee in Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union of University of Science.
- Member of the Standing Committee in Ho Chi Minh Communist Youth Union of the Faculty ofInformation Technology.

### **REFERENCES**

### **Assoc. Prof. Minh-Triet TRAN**

Vice President

University of Science, VNU-HCMC

Email: tmtriet@hcmus.edu.vn

### **Prof. Davide BALZAROTTI**

Department Digital Security

EURECOM, 06410 Biot, France

Email: davide.balzarotti@eurecom.fr

### **NEWS**

DEC 2020	I was the coach of the Computer Security team who won the
	Second Prize of the Cyber SEA Game 2020
	https://tinyurl.com/ydg6uy8e
NOV 2020	I was the coach of the Computer Security team who was the
	Champion of the ASEAN Student Contest on Information Security
	2020
	https://tinyurl.com/yc3lq4ou
FEB 2020	I gave a Web-Mobile Security Training for Viettel Digital - Ha Noi
NOV 2019	I gave a talk at Vietnam Information Security Day 2019 in GEM
	Center. The topic is "Cybersecurity in the Age of Industry 4.0: How
	to survive new threats"